{
    "subject": "Abhishek_Bachchan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Aishwarya_Rai",
    "human_readable": "Abhishek Bachchan is married to Aishwarya Rai.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9826081395149231,
            "question": "Is there a famous Bollywood marriage between Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9591705203056335,
            "question": "To whom is Abhishek Bachchan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9583555459976196,
            "question": "Are Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9519681334495544,
            "question": "Is Abhishek Bachchan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9067276120185852,
            "question": "Who are Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935331702232361,
            "question": "Who is married to Aishwarya Rai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8931385278701782,
            "question": "Who is Aishwarya Rai married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8259502053260803,
            "question": "What is the name of Abhishek Bachchan's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816376805305481,
            "question": "What is the name of Abhishek Bachchan's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18434537947177887,
            "question": "Name the celebrity couple."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abhishek Bachchan is married to Aishwarya Rai.",
            "html": "yago_29534_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Abhishek Bachchan's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_29534_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Abhishek Bachchan's wife?",
            "html": "yago_29534_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Aishwarya Rai married to?",
            "html": "yago_29534_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29534_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The answer to the query \"Abhishek Bachchan is married to Aishwarya Rai.\" would be:\n\n{'output': 'yes'} \n\nThis is because all the provided context information mentions Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai as a couple, with multiple articles confirming their marriage, celebrating their anniversary, and mentioning them together at various events."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai Bachchan are a well-known couple in Bollywood, with multiple references to their marriage. For instance, from the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_29534/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt`, it is stated: \"Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai Bachchan, one of Bollywood's most celebrated couples, tied the knot on April 20, 2007, in a grand ceremony that captured the nation's attention.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}